A Guide to the China Medical Board records, RG 2, Accession 2014:022, SG 1 FA1292
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowships and Grants, 1951-1996, 2002; 2
  - 67-936-2, Chulalongkorn University, Fellow, Voravarn, Twinsri, 1966-1969 (Box 93, Folder 1595)
  - 70-141-59, Chulalongkorn University, Fellow, Wattanaponsiri, Artorntip, 1971-1972 (Box 93, Folder 1596)
  - 73-318-4, Chulalongkorn University, Fellow, Wongwiwat, Mai, 1972-1973, 1975 (Box 94, Folder 1597)
  - 68-086-30, 69-086-72, Chulalongkorn University, Fellow, Yunibhand, Premchai, 1969-1971 (Box 94, Folder 1598)
  - 72-266 (37), Chulalongkorn University, Regional Fellowship, 1975-1976 (Box 94, Folder 1599)
  - 73-329 (10), Chulalongkorn University, Fellowship Allocation, Dean's Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 94, Folder 1600)
  - 73-318-4, Chulalongkorn University, Fellowship Grant, 1973 (Box 94, Folder 1601)
  - 70-131-57, 72-266-8, Chulalongkorn University, Fellow, Lohsoonthorn, Paibool, 1971-1972 (Box 94, Folder 1602)
  - University of Chiang Mai (UCM)-University of Illinois, Affiliation Program, General Correspondence, 1961-1971 (Box 94, Folder 1603)
  - 61-617, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Books, 1961-1963 (Box 94, Folder 1604)
  - 63-688, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Research, 1963-1964 (Box 94, Folder 1605)
  - 64-797, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Library Support, 1964-1966 (Box 94, Folder 1606)
  - 65-829, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Equipment-Medicine & Nursing, 1963-1969 (Box 94, Folder 1607)
  - 65-830, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Equipment-Public Health Training Center, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 1608)
  - 65-839, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Equipment-Experimental Surgery Laboratory, 1965-1969 (Box 94, Folder 1609)
  - 65-862, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Library Support, 1965-1969 (Box 94, Folder 1610)
  - 68-050, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Library Support-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1967-1971 (Box 94, Folder 1611)
  - 69-080, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1969-1972 (Box 94, Folder 1612)
  - 70-168, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1974 (Box 94, Folder 1613)
  - 70-169, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1972 (Box 94, Folder 1614)
  - 70-170, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Library Support-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1973 (Box 94, Folder 1615)
  - 71-192, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1974 (Box 95, Folder 1616)
  - 71-225, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1973 (Box 95, Folder 1617)
  - 71-226, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1974 (Box 95, Folder 1618)
  - 72-259 I, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972-1976 (Box 95, Folder 1619)
  - 72-286 I, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1972-1973, 1975-1976 (Box 95, Folder 1620)
  - 73-315 I, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Research-General Correspondence, 1973-1975, 1977-1980 (Box 95, Folder 1621)
  - 74-341 I, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Research-General Correspondence, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 1622)
  - 68-022-2, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellow, Amatayakul, Kosin, 1966, 1968-1969 (Box 95, Folder 1623)
  - 67-936-1, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellow, Kasemsant, Dhanyasbhak, 1967 (Box 95, Folder 1624)
  - 66-896-36, 67-937-27, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellow, Khamboonruang, Chirasak, 1966-1967 (Box 95, Folder 1625)
  - 68-022-56, 69-086-46, 70-141-17, 70-141-23, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellow, Khanjanasthiti, Parimondh, 1969-1971 (Box 95, Folder 1626)
  - 70-141-14, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellow, Pan-In, Saungwian, 1970-1971 (Box 95, Folder 1627)
  - 68-022-40, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellow, Promkutkao, Choomnoom, 1968-1970 (Box 95, Folder 1628)
  - 69-086-18, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellow, Santadusit, Aroon, 1969-1970 (Box 95, Folder 1629)
  - 62-647-1, 63-694-1, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellow, Suchinda, Subharp, 1962-1963 (Box 95, Folder 1630)
  - 64-762-30, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellow, Sujavanich, Yongyoot, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 1631)
  - 65-834-7, 65-868-11, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellow, Tejasen, Tejatat, 1964-1967 (Box 95, Folder 1632)
  - 65-834-55, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellow, Thanangkul, Ousa, 1965-1968 (Box 95, Folder 1633)
  - 69-086-27, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellow, Thitasut, Mukda, 1969-1971, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 1634)
  - 71-203-15, 73-318-6, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellow, Vinicchykul, Rachanee, 1969-1970, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 1635)
  - 72-266-17, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellow, Inboriboon, Prayool, 1972-1974, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 1636)
  - 72-266 (38), University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Regional Fellowship, 1976 (Box 96, Folder 1637)
  - 73-318-6, 73-318-13, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellowship Grant, 1973-1974, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 1638)
  - 73-329-11, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellowship Allocation, 1975-1976 (Box 96, Folder 1639)
  - 75-343-2, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellowship Grant, 1978, 1980 (Box 96, Folder 1640)
  - 78-373-2, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Fellowships, 1979, 1981-1982 (Box 96, Folder 1641)
  - 61-596, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Visiting Professor, Netsky, Martin G., 1960-1963 (Box 96, Folder 1642)
  - 61-618, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), School of Nursing, Equipment, 1961-1964 (Box 96, Folder 1643)
  - 75-343-1, 78-373-12, 87-467-4, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), School of Nursing, Fellowships, 1977, 1979-1983, 1985, 1988-1991 (Box 96, Folder 1644)
  - 77-366, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), School of Nursing, Nursing Research, Education, & Training, 1977-1984, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 1645)
  - 88-501, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), School of Nursing, Fax-Purchase & Installation, 1988 (Box 96, Folder 1646)
  - 75-343-1, 78-373-12, 78-373-19, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Faculty of Nursing, Eamjoy, Wanpen, 1973-1985, 1987-1990 (Box 96, Folder 1647)
  - 66-896-23, 67-938-24, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), School of Nursing, Fellow, Hutangkura, La-aw, 1966-1968, 1972 (Box 96, Folder 1648)
  - 69-086-34, 70-141-40, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), School of Nursing, Fellow, Mahanpab, Tatsana, 1968-1972 (Box 96, Folder 1649)
  - 68-022-10, 68-022-57, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), School of Nursing, Fellow, Roongsuwan, Charoonsri, 1967-1970 (Box 96, Folder 1650)
  - 70-141-36, 70-141-61, 72-266-14, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), School of Nursing, Fellow, Swasdiraksa, Praneet, 1969, 1971-1973 (Box 97, Folder 1651)
  - 70-141-36, 70-141-61, 72-266-14, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), School of Nursing, Fellow, Swasdiraksa, Praneet, 1969, 1971-1973 (Box 97, Folder 1651A)
    Restricted-Personal information
  - 87-467-5, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Faculty of Nursing, Tienswad, Sujitra, 1990-1994 (Box 97, Folder 1652)
  - 87-497-5, University of Chiang Mai (UCM), Faculty of Nursing, Tienswad, Sujitra, 1990-1994 (Box 97, Folder 1652A)
  - 76-357, Chulalongkorn University, Endowment Fund for Medical Research, 1976-1982, 1984-1988, 1995 (Box 97, Folder 1653-1654)
  - 77-361, Chulalongkorn University, Faculty of Medicine, Endowment Fund for Staff Development, 1976-1995 (Box 97, Folder 1655)
  - 81-407, Chulalongkorn University, Endowment Fund for Medical Library, 1980-1992, 1994-1995 (Box 97, Folder 1656)
  - 83-426, Chulalongkorn University, Faculty of Medicine, Endowment Fund for General Development, 1983-1995 (Box 98, Folder 1657)
  - CM 272, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Microscopes, 1952-1954 (Box 98, Folder 1658)
  - CM 355, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Laboratory, 1955-1959 (Box 98, Folder 1659)
  - CM 356, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Books, Journals, & Equipment, 1955, 1957-1959 (Box 98, Folder 1660)
  - 57-4008, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Research-Clinical Pathology, 1957-1958 (Box 98, Folder 1661)
  - 58-461, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Books, Journals, Furnishing, & Equipment, 1958, 1960-1961 (Box 98, Folder 1662)
  - 59-470, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Teaching & Research, 1958-1961 (Box 98, Folder 1663)
  - 61-578, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Books, Journals, Equipment-Library Support, 1961-1964 (Box 98, Folder 1664)
  - 61-579, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment, 1961-1964 (Box 98, Folder 1665)
  - 61-619, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Hematology, 1961-1966 (Box 98, Folder 1666)
  - 63-686, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Tissue Culture Laboratory, 1962-1966 (Box 98, Folder 1667)
  - 63-710, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Supplies & Equipment, 1963-1965 (Box 98, Folder 1668)
  - 63-730, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Supplies & Equipment-Teaching & Research, 1962-1966 (Box 98, Folder 1669)
  - 64-754, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Histochemistry, 1964-1966 (Box 98, Folder 1670)
  - 64-755, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Blood Coagulation Laboratory, 1963-1965 (Box 98, Folder 1671)
  - 64-793, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Radiology, 1964-1965 (Box 98, Folder 1672)
  - 64-794, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Library Support-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1963-1966, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1673)
  - 65-826, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Cytogenetics, 1965, 1967-1968 (Box 98, Folder 1674)
  - 65-827, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Medical Illustration, 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 1675)
  - 65-828, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Cardiac Surgery, 1965-1969 (Box 98, Folder 1676)
  - 65-859, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Physiology, Pharmacology, & Student Laboratory, 1965-1966, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 1677)
  - 65-860, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Teaching & Research, 1965-1969 (Box 99, Folder 1678)
  - 66-892, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Pulmonary Function Laboratory, 1966-1969 (Box 99, Folder 1679)
  - 66-924, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Reserach, 1966-1968 (Box 99, Folder 1680)
  - 67-983, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Library Support, 1967-1972 (Box 99, Folder 1681)
  - 67-984, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Pharmacology, Physiology, & Biochemistry, 1967-1970 (Box 99, Folder 1682)
  - 67-952, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Microbiology, 1966-1968 (Box 99, Folder 1683)
  - 68-017, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment, 1965, 1967-1969 (Box 99, Folder 1684)
  - 68-078, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment, 1968-1971 (Box 99, Folder 1685)
  - 69-109, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Blood Bank Equipment, 1969-1973 (Box 99, Folder 1686)
    2014:022, SG 1:071
  - 69-109, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Blood Bank Equipment, 1969-1973; 2014:022, SG 1:071
  - 70-133, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Experimental Surgery, 1970-1971 (Box 99, Folder 1687)
  - 70-134, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Cardiac Laboratory, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1971, 1973 (Box 99, Folder 1688)
  - 70-164, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1973 (Box 99, Folder 1689)
  - 70-165, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Equipment-Endocrinology, General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1974 (Box 99, Folder 1690)
  - 70-166, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Library Support-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1970-1973 (Box 99, Folder 1691)
  - 71-190, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 1692)
  - 72-223 I, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Research-General Correspondence & Original Orders, 1971-1972, 1974-1975 (Box 99, Folder 1693)
  - 72-256 I, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Medical Faculty Equipment, 1972 (Box 99, Folder 1694)
  - 72-257 I, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Medical Faculty Research, 1972, 1974-1975 (Box 99, Folder 1695)
  - 73-316 I, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Faculty of Nursing-Equipment/Self Instructional Unit, 1973-1976 (Box 100, Folder 1696)
  - 73-318-3, 73-329-13, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Faculty of Nursing, Boontong, Tassana, 1972, 1974-1977 (Box 100, Folder 1697)
  - 73-329-5, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Faculty of Nursing-Fellowship Allocation, 1974-1976, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 1698)
  - 67-938-38, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Ariyamitr, Prabhand, 1967-1968 (Box 100, Folder 1700)
  - 68-022-51, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Balankura, Chira, 1969-1971 (Box 100, Folder 1700)
  - 67-938-59, 68-022-23, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Bhanganda, Kasian, 1968-1969 (Box 100, Folder 1701)
  - 58-429-14, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Binbakya, Bidyabhed, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 1702)
  - 71-230-4, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Boonyapisit, Sasiprapa Tuchinda, 1971-1973, 1976-1977 (Box 100, Folder 1703)
  - 72-266-3, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Boonyapisit, Viravidh, 1972-1973 (Box 100, Folder 1704)
  - 58-429-11, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Buri, Prem, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 1705)
  - CM 371, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Chamlong, Harinasuta, 1956, 1958-1959 (Box 100, Folder 1706)
  - 58-474-8, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Chamriang, Kooramsuvan, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 1707)
  - 61-591-42, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Chandanayingyong, Dasnayanee, 1962-1963, 1965-1967 (Box 100, Folder 1708)
  - CM 311-21, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Chindabha, Sayanha, 1955 (Box 100, Folder 1709)
  - 67-938-64, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Chulkarat, Prapassorn, 1966-1969 (Box 100, Folder 1710)
  - 67-938-42, 69-086-8, 69-086-21, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Goysookho, Vibha, 1966-1970 (Box 100, Folder 1711)
  - 66-896-53, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Hungspreugs, Suwana, 1966-1968 (Box 101, Folder 1712)
  - 73-318-3 I, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Ibrahim, Farida, 1972-1975 (Box 101, Folder 1713)
  - 72-266-16, 73-318-3, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Jugpet, Vipa, 1972-1974 (Box 101, Folder 1714)
  - CM 311-2, CM 311-25, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Kallapravit, Boonanake, 1954-1955 (Box 101, Folder 1715)
  - 63-694-39, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Ketusinh, Ouay, 1963-1966 (Box 101, Folder 1716)
  - 64-762-47, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Kolatat, Thongchatr, 1964-1966 (Box 101, Folder 1717)
  - 69-086-1, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Kongsampan, Sophon, 1968-1970 (Box 101, Folder 1718)
  - 65-868-1, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Kritalugsana, Sompool, 1959, 1961-1962, 1964-1967 (Box 101, Folder 1719)
  - 63-694-9, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Limphanichakarn, Sapha, 1963-1965 (Box 101, Folder 1720)
  - 60-541-39, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Mettiyawongse, Sorn, 1961 (Box 101, Folder 1721)
  - CM 279-3, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Niyomsen, Song-Grant, 1954 (Box 101, Folder 1722)
  - 65-868-14, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Pacharee, Prasert, 1964-1968 (Box 101, Folder 1723)
  - 66-896-54, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Panich, Vicharn, 1966-1968 (Box 101, Folder 1724)
  - 58-429-13, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Pansuwana, Panpit, 1958, 1960-1961 (Box 101, Folder 1725)
  - 69-086-2, 69-086-59, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Pholnuangma, Bangorn, 1968-1971 (Box 101, Folder 1726)
  - 73-318-3 (R), Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Rabieb, Pensri, 1972-1975 (Box 101, Folder 1727)
  - 68-022-033, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Prachuabomh, Kampol, 1968-1970 (Box 101, Folder 1728)
  - 71-203-11, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Sangvichien, Sanjai, 1971-1973 (Box 101, Folder 1729)
  - 59-474-19, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Sangvichien, Sood, 1959-1960 (Box 101, Folder 1730)
  - 65-834-16, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Singhprasert, Pranee, 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 1731)
  - CM 362-17, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Songthanasak, Prathamb, 1957 (Box 102, Folder 1732)
  - 62-647-43, 64-762-18, 65-834-25, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Sophanodorn, Kanchana, 1963-1965 (Box 102, Folder 1733)
  - 61-591-3, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Sukhavachana, Dhara, 1961-1962 (Box 102, Folder 1734)
  - 65-834-57, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Suphaphongs, Nit, 1964-1966, 1969-1972 (Box 102, Folder 1735)
  - 60-541-13, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Tansurat, Pradit, 1960-1961 (Box 102, Folder 1736)
  - 65-834-18, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Thasnakorn, Prayad, 1965-1966, 1969-1970 (Box 102, Folder 1737)
  - 68-011-1, 68-022-64, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Thavilab, Vichien, 1967-1969, 1971-1972, 1974 (Box 102, Folder 1738)
  - 58-429-12, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Titthasiri, Natha, 1958, 1960 (Box 102, Folder 1739)
  - CM 327-13, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Tosayanonda, Songchat, 1955-1957 (Box 102, Folder 1740)
  - 70-141-19, 72-266-1, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Unakul, Woranooj, 1970-1974 (Box 102, Folder 1741)
  - CM 259-1, CM 279-5, 60-541-14, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Uthai, Dhutoyabhodi, 1952-1955, 1960-1961 (Box 102, Folder 1742)
  - 68-022-45, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Uthai, Dhtiyabhodhi, 1968-1969 (Box 102, Folder 1743)
  - CM 362-16, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Utit, Sukatat, 1957 (Box 102, Folder 1744)
  - 63-694-44, 65-634-4, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Viseskul, Vinitha, 1963-1966 (Box 102, Folder 1745)
  - 59-474-43, 60-541-28, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Vitoon, Osathanondh, 1960-1961, 1963-1964 (Box 102, Folder 1746)
  - 71-203-33, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Wasi, Chantapong, 1971-1973 (Box 102, Folder 1747)
  - 61-591-45, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Fellow, Watanavit, Tongpoon, 1962-1964, 1969 (Box 102, Folder 1748)
  - CM 357, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Consultant, Medical Education-First Thai National Conference, 1955-1957 (Box 103, Folder 1749)
  - 57-421, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Visiting Professor, Bowman, Karl M., 1957-1960 (Box 103, Folder 1750)
  - 69-092, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Visiting Consultant, Guy, L. Ruth-American Association Blood Banks, 1968-1971 (Box 103, Folder 1751)
  - 69-110, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Visiting Professor, Oppenheimer, Morton J.-The London Company, 1968-1971 (Box 103, Folder 1752)
  - 63-706, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Consultant, Paton, Bruce C., 1963-1964 (Box 103, Folder 1753)
  - 57-422, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Visiting Consultant, Reich, Lydia F., 1957-1960 (Box 103, Folder 1754)
  - 58-462, Mahidol University, Siriraj Hospital, Visiting Professor, Rosahn, Paul D., 1958-1962 (Box 103, Folder 1755)
  - 60-018, Mahidol University, Ramathibodi Hospital, Equipment-Biology, 1968-1970 (Box 103, Folder 1756)
  - 67-938-41, Mahidol University, Ramathibodi Hospital, Fellow, Chindavanig, Supis, 1967-1968 (Box 103, Folder 1757)
  - 67-938-58, Mahidol University, Ramathibodi Hospital, Fellow, Munying, Surat, 1964, 1967-1969 (Box 103, Folder 1758)
  - 77-367, Mahidol University, Faculty of Public Health, Endowment Fund for Public Health, 1977-1989 (Box 103, Folder 1759)
  - 77-367, Mahidol University, Faculty of Public Health, Endowment Fund for Public Health, 1977-1989 (Box 104, Folder 1760)
  - 70-141-16, Mahidol University, Faculty of Public Health, Fellow, Kasiwat, Paichit, 1970-1972 (Box 104, Folder 1761)
  - 70-141-13, 71-203-6, 71-141-68, Mahidol University, Faculty of Public Health, Fellow, Kongsiri, Likhit, 1970-1974 (Box 104, Folder 1762)
  - 71-203-14, 73-318-3, Mahidol University, Faculty of Public Health, Fellow, Suepsaman, Banchong, 1971-1973 (Box 104, Folder 1763)
  - 71-203-27, 73-318-3, Mahidol University, Faculty of Public Health, Fellow, Temcharoen, Prasong, 1971-1972 (Box 104, Folder 1764)
  - Consultant 1968, Keefer, Chester S., Administrative Budget, 1965-1966, 1968 (Box 104, Folder 1765)
  - 59-490, 60-542, Consultant, Loucks, Harold H., 1959-1961 (Box 104, Folder 1766)
  - 61-593, 62-651, Consultant, Loucks, Harold H., 1962 (Box 104, Folder 1767)
  - 62-651, 63-699, Consultant, Loucks, Harold H., 1963-1964 (Box 104, Folder 1768)
  - 63-699, 64-766, 65-838, 66-900, 67-941, Consultant, Loucks, Harold H., 1964-1972 (Box 105, Folder 1769)
  - 64-736, Consultant, Meader, John W., 1963, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 1770)
  - 60-521, Consultant, Moore, Robert A., 1960-1961 (Box 105, Folder 1771)
  - 63-733, Consultant, Moore, Robert A., 1963-1964 (Box 105, Folder 1772)
  - 64-801, Consultant, Wescoe, W. Clarke, 1964-1965 (Box 105, Folder 1773)
  - 78-372, Columbia University, van Dyke, Harry B., Lectureship in Pharmacology, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 1774)
  - Conferences/Meetings, General, A-Z, 1971-1973, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 1175)
  - Conference/Meeting, Conference on Medical Education-Foreign Scholars, General Correspondence, 1959, 1962-1970 (Box 105, Folder 1776)
  - CM 377, Conference on Medical Education, #1, University of Wisconsin Medical School, 1956-1957 (Box 105, Folder 1777)
  - 57-424, Conference on Medical Education, #2, University of Wisconsin Medical School, 1957-1958, 1961 (Box 105, Folder 1778)
  - 58-468, Conference on Medical Education for Foreign Scholars, #3, State University of Iowa, 1958-1961 (Box 105, Folder 1779)
  - 59-519, Conference on Medical Education, #4, University of Colorado, 1959-1960 (Box 105, Folder 1780)
  - 60-565, 63-677, Conference on Medical Education for Foreign Scholars, #5, University of Rochester, 1960-1963 (Box 105, Folder 1781)
  - 61-622, Conference on Medical Education, #6, University of Chicago, 1961-1963 (Box 105, Folder 1782)
  - 62-675, Conference on Medical Education for Foreign Scholars, #7, University of California San Francisco, 1962-1963 (Box 105, Folder 1783)
  - Conference on Medical Education for Foreign Scholars, #8, University of Kansas, 1963-1964 (Box 105, Folder 1784)
  - Conference on Medical Education for Foreign Scholars, #9, University of Virginia, 1965 (Box 105, Folder 1785)
  - Conference on Medical Education for Foreign Scholars, #10, University of Minnesota, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 1786)
  - Conference on Medical Education, #11, Duke University, 1967 (Box 106, Folder 1787)
  - Conference on Medical Education, #12, George Washington University, 1968 (Box 106, Folder 1788)
  - Conference on Medical Education, #13, University of Missouri, 1969 (Box 106, Folder 1789)
  - Conference on Medical Education, #14, Case Western University, 1970 (Box 106, Folder 1790)
  - Conference on Medical Education for Foreign Scholars, #15, University of Cincinnati, 1971-1972 (Box 106, Folder 1791)
  - Conference on Medical Education for Foreign Scholars, #16, Harvard Medical School, 1970-1972 (Box 106, Folder 1792)
  - 72-293, Baylor University, Instrumentation Workshop, Scholarships, 1972-1974 (Box 106, Folder 1793)
  - CM 324, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1954-1956 (Box 106, Folder 1794)
  - CM 383, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1956-1958, 1960 (Box 106, Folder 1795)
  - 58-434, Contingent Fund, Donations, 1956, 1958-1960 (Box 106, Folder 1796)